<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ian Maddaus</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ian Maddaus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BFG Repo-Cleaner - Deleting Large File From Git</title>
      <link>/post/deleting-large-file-from-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/deleting-large-file-from-git/</guid>
      <description>BFG Repo-Cleaner is the best way to delete a large file from a git repository that you&amp;rsquo;ve already committed.
When a file is committed to a repository, it stays in the repository&amp;rsquo;s history, and is uploaded to a remote repository, even if you remove it in a subsequent commit. This allows a user to undo a subsequent commit and return to a previous version without losing any files. However, users may want to completely delete a file that is too large for the remote server or could have sensitive information stored in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Voice - This Passive Voice Sentence Was Written By Zombies</title>
      <link>/post/passive-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/passive-voice/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few articles about using the passive voice. I could provide my own commentary but these articles are better than anything that I would write. In short, people often use the passive voice excessively or incorrectly, but the passive voice is an effective way to describe a passive subject or a victim.
 Poynter Institute - NPR tornado report reveals the elements of vivid newswriting Poynter Institute - In praise of the passive voice Poynter Institute - Blindsided: How Christie used passive verbs to turn himself into a victim NY Times - The Pleasures and Perils of the Passive  How To Identify The Passive Voice I was stumped when I first started looking for the passive voice in my own writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Manage Multiple Versions of Python on a Mac</title>
      <link>/post/manage-multiple-versions-python-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/manage-multiple-versions-python-mac/</guid>
      <description>Summary Warnings Mac OS needs python Other projects may need specific versions of python  Installation python.org Homebrew Anaconda  PATH and .bash_profile PATH .bash_profile  Homebrew - pyenv Pyenv Local Pyenv Global  Locate Python Uninstall python python.org Homebrew Troubleshooting Uninstall Python from Pyenv  Anaconda  Additional Resources XKCD   Summary It’s easy to install multiple versions of python on a Mac computer using installers from python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guides For Learning Git &amp; Github</title>
      <link>/post/guides-for-learning-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/guides-for-learning-git/</guid>
      <description>These are five great guides to using git:
 Happy Git With R Data Carpentry - Version Control with Git RStudio Webinar - Managing Github and RStudio. Git Immersion - use git in the command line. Github Guides - Hello World  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Note on A blogdown Tutorial</title>
      <link>/post/another-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/another-note/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered an awesome tutorial on blogdown written by Alison. I have to admit this is the best blogdown tutorial I have seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quick Note on Two Beautiful Websites</title>
      <link>/post/a-quick-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-quick-note/</guid>
      <description>To me, the two most impressive websites based on blogdown are:
 Rob J Hyndman&amp;rsquo;s personal website. Live Free or Dichotomize by Lucy and Nick et al.  I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Plain Markdown Post</title>
      <link>/post/2016-02-14-hello-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2016-02-14-hello-markdown/</guid>
      <description>This sample post is mainly for blogdown users. If you do not use blogdown, you can skip the first section.
1. Markdown or R Markdown This is a post written in plain Markdown (*.md) instead of R Markdown (*.Rmd). The major differences are:
 You cannot run any R code in a plain Markdown document, whereas in an R Markdown document, you can embed R code chunks (```{r}); A plain Markdown post is rendered through Blackfriday, and an R Markdown document is compiled by rmarkdown and Pandoc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>